<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dustin Pedlow</title>
    <link>https://dustinpedlow.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dustin Pedlow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 20:52:22 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dustinpedlow.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A sshlockout Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://dustinpedlow.xyz/home/a-sshlockout-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 20:52:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dustinpedlow.xyz/home/a-sshlockout-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>This is a quick look at sshlockout and how to effectively use it to ban attackers.
The sshlockout program is a extra layer of security that bans IP addresses that have reached a maximum threshold of failed password attempts. The sshlockout program originates from DragonFlyBSD and has been ported to OpenBSD. If you&amp;rsquo;re from the Linux world this is similar to Fail2Ban and is a very simple program. When sshlockout is setup using the settings shown in the manpage it will ban any IP address that exceeds 5 incorrect passwords in one hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Setup a OpenBSD Website</title>
      <link>https://dustinpedlow.xyz/home/how-to-setup-a-openbsd-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 22:10:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dustinpedlow.xyz/home/how-to-setup-a-openbsd-website/</guid>
      <description>This is a simple tutorial on creating a website in the cloud using OpenBSD, HTTPD and HUGO. This is based on the same steps I used to create the website you&amp;rsquo;re reading this on. My main focus was on security, minimalism and reliability. I choose OpenBSD because It has amazing security settings out of the box and it&amp;rsquo;s very lightweight. This tutorial assumes you are a beginner but have some basic knowledge of DNS and unix commands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://dustinpedlow.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dustinpedlow.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello internet! My name is Dustin and I am currently a Network Administration Technology student at my local college. In my spare time I enjoy working on my homelab and learning about both Windows and Unix-like operating systems. I have a love of Linux and the opensource project that power it. I also like learning about cyber security and how to make systems more secure and reliable. I am a bit of a hardware enthusiast and love to build/upgrade computers and spend hours tweaking the performance and power useage to fit the use of the computer or server.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
